good coaching, uh, productive team.
Anyway, it's a, this will be a big
challenge on the road at their place,
but, uh, once again, looking forward to
this. This is, uh, this is why you're in
it. So, questions.
>> I was a 11 personnel guy forever. I
mean, that was kind of what they did.
Ton of 13 this year. Seems like a pretty
>> drastic switch. What What do you see on
tape when you look at that? What are
they doing? And, um, you know, why are
they so so successful doing it? Well, I
I think a lot of this under center run
um gives them a chance to um you know to
really lean on you a little bit. You
know, that's where a lot of it has
changed is uh there's there's more of a
concerted effort in the run game I feel
like to be um you know to apply pressure
on you. Um, I think that gives some of
those receivers a break, you know. Um,
that helps a little bit. And now you
bring them back in at 11, uh, you know,
it's it's just a good change up and I
think there's predictability in 13.
Normally, you know what you're going to
get. Sometimes in 12, you don't know if
you're going to get nickel or base
defense. So, that's another reason. They
know what they're going to attack,
right? U, they know probably the
defense, the fronts, the coverages. That
helps. Um, and they got they got tight
ends. I mean, they've got some tight
ends that are they're versatile, can do
a little bit of everything. That's
always going to help. Um, you know, and
I think uh McVeyy's always done a good
job of
uh putting players in the best position
to have success using using the roster,
the totality of it as much as you can
use your personnel. If you've got it,
use it. And uh he does a great job with
that.
>> Corm has uh spearheaded some success in
the run game for them. Just how have you
seen that pick up over the last four
games or so? How much more dangerous
does it make their passing offense when
their run game is clicking like that?
>> Well, ju just like no different than us.
I mean, if you can run the ball, you you
you're uh it becomes very dangerous
because uh now just the play pass off of
that, you know, you have to honor the
run cuz you popped a couple there.
There's a concerted effort to uh you
know, to hand the ball off and uh and so
you have no choice. You got to fill the
gaps and then you play pass off of it
and you got a guy like Stafford back
there throwing. I mean, he's an accurate
passer. He's on point, you know,
obviously he's done this for a long
time. He knows the coverages. I mean, he
just, you know, he's playing at a high
level once again. Um,
uh, but like Corm, he's a good back and,
uh, you know, it they've got a little
bit of a one-two punch over there. Both
of those guys are really good. Um, you
know, they gave him a load yesterday.
You know, he rushed for over a hundred.
Um, so I I think it's uh it's a good
change up. I think both of those guys,
they're a little different, but yet to
me, they're both powerbacks. They're
both able to go downhill and slice and
get under you and and move [music] the
move the pile. Um, you know, they're
quick, they're explosive, they're
twitchy, they're versatile. So, uh, to
answer your question, it helps them. I
mean, it certainly doesn't hurt them.
Uh, it just gives them another element
there.
>> Back to news from from last week. Brian
obviously out for the season, the
Achilles. What sort of mood is he in and
what sort of bind are you guys in at
safety right now in helping Kirby help
that maybe coming back?
>> Well, anytime you lose somebody like BB,
it's going to hurt. I mean, he's a
productive player. You know, he's a he's
uh he's,
you know, he's he's an outstanding
football player and uh and he's a he's a
team guy. He's a great locker room guy.
Teammates love him. So, you lose all of
that, you know, and that that hurts.
That's going to hurt you any time. Now,
that being said, Maddox went in there
for him the other day and we thought he
did a hell of a job. He really did. I
mean, he he played his tail off, which
is why he's here because he's a football
guy and uh he's got versatility. Nickel
that can play safety. Um, man, he put
out a lot of fires back there for us.
Made quite a few plays. So, that's
encouraging. Um,
so, you know, we got him, we got DT back
there. Um, you know, Howlet's played
there before. We're going to see if
Kirby, you know, see where he's at. Get
him some reps here in practice. And so,
um, we, you know, we're we're good, man.
We signed Kazee, see where he's at
practice squad. Um,
so we we got options here, but, you
know, it's like anything. You lose a
good player, it hurts, but but, uh, it's
not like we're in dire straits.
>> What's Harvard's status? We saw him exit
on Thursday.
>> Harper's another one. We'll see. He's
still in concussion protocol. no
setbacks, but yet, you know, I I don't
know if we're going to have the runway
to get him or not. Um, you know, and I'm
just kind of as of right now, I'm like
until we get further along here, I'm
just kind of we'll see. Um, but
certainly if we could get Harper back,
that would be really good, too.
>> Yeah. Just kind of the mindset. Final
quarter of the season. Last couple of
years you were being chased. Now you're
kind of trying to chase teams down over
this final quarter. Just how you
approach that?
>> Same. Uh, it really is the same
approach. Nothing is nothing has changed
um just in that regard. You got to win.
You know, we had to win last year.
That's that's the way it felt. Um you
know, you never felt like you could uh
take a breath last year. You you're
you're constantly trying to you know, it
was for something different, but yet
you're, you know, you're trying to get
the one seed, you're trying to get that
home game, you're trying to get the
throughout the PL, all this stuff. And
now it's no different. It's just we got
to win. We need to win. Uh you know,
we're trying to get back to that spot.
So, all that matters is this one just
like it was Dallas, man. We had to win
that game. We had to find a way to win
that game. And uh we did everything
right. Not everything, but but relative
to that game and everybody doing their
job, we we did what we needed to do to
win it. Played complimentary football.
We got to do it again on the road versus
the Rams. Very good team. Uh playing at
a very high level. So, and and we got to
play better. We got to play better to
beat this team that we're getting ready
to face. And we will. We can do that. We
can play better. We will play better.
>> Sorry about that, Dan. Um, when when you
play a quarterback like Stafford that's
so good at manipulating the safeties
with his his eyes and you have the
moving pieces you do there, what what is
maybe some of the the emphasis coaching
pointwise to, you know, make sure those
guys are are playing with good eyes,
with good discipline in that that that
spot. Well, I think it's it's just that
you do the best you can to to uh
you know, for them to understand that he
will try to manipulate you. Now, you
also,
you know, at some point, um you can't
just sit there,
you know, at some point you have to move
and and he knows that, too. I mean,
that's why he's good at what he does. He
knows that, too. But at some point, you
know, if you just sit there and he's
baiting you. Well, if you don't move, he
don't throw it, you know. So, you still
got to move. It's just understand you
could be he could be trying to move you
here a little bit. He could be trying to
manip manipulate you. You got to play
your keys. And then, look, we got to get
to them up front. You know, we got to
cause some disruption. Like last week,
that was one of the things we did a
really good job of. We were able to to
disrupt um you know, what they were
doing and it it paid huge dividends,
man. It got us three takeaways or really
two. Um so, you know, we and a lateral
that was huge. Um so, we got to do that
again. You know, the front is just as
important as the back end. Um you know,
these guys will understand what they're
getting ready to face. We know this is a
this is an outstanding quarterback and
he's got weapons and uh they're
versatile and like I said, very good
coaching and and uh so, you know, we got
to find a way to get takeaways. You got
to do it. We got to do it again. Do
>> you like having these these like mini
buys? I mean, you got another one coming
up in a couple weeks, but how does that
help the team? And then flip side of
that is, you know, uh first game of the
season coming off the buy, you guys lost
those games. So, how do you make sure
the guys are where they need to be
Sunday?
>> Well, that's a downer, Dave. Thank you
for that.
>> Jeez. Well, I don't know, Dave. Well, I
guess we'll find out. Uh
yeah, I do. I mean, listen, that that's
a hard stretch we just came from. Just
like Dallas just came off that stretch,
too. That's We had to do that last year.
That's difficult. Um, you know, it it's
not easy on the players. It's not easy
on the coaches. Um,
but but it's it's what's on the
schedule. You do it and you find a way
to win. Um, and we did that. But you
need the breather. You know, these guys
needed that. And uh, so you get a couple
of days off and uh, like I said the
other day, catch your breath. And now we
we get ready for these guys. get ready
for the Rams and um you know we got to
put together a good game plan which
we're trying to do right now. Uh and
these guys come in and we'll be smart
about how we work this week too. We
we'll get some work but we're also I
also know what we just came from. Um so
we'll we'll get some work but we're
going to be smart and there'll be some
mental reps in there, some walkthrough
reps, but and then we'll move a little
bit but want to make sure we got plenty
in the tank this week.
>> You said after uh after the Dallas game
that was the best complimentary football
you guys have played all season. Uh why
why do you think that was?
>> Well, maybe a long time. It's been a
while.
>> Um why do you think that was and then
how do you replicate that again?
>> Well, I I just think it was um look, the
the takeaways go a long way, you know.
Um I think between here here's when you
get the returns that we were able to
get. Tom Kennedy was big for us. The
return game was huge. You get the field
position you're able to get, you know,
Fox punts it, man. We pin him inside the
four. We get a stop was dang near a
safety. Um, we get the takeaway, we turn
it into seven, right? We get another
takeaway, we turn it into seven. There's
14 points. We get a takeaway at the end,
turns to a victory, we take a knee. Um,
man, we were just clicking it all at the
right time. And it was like when if
something if something um
uh went against us, we lost a little bit
of momentum, man. The other unit picked
it up, you know, they shut it down. Um,
so they score over there, man. We score.
They score. We score. We fizzle out.
defense gets a takeaway or gets the
stop. Um, they make a play, man. Special
teams, we get it to the 45. There's a
return to the minus 45. Those are huge.
And, uh, that's that's when all the
other stuff doesn't matter. When you can
do that in a game, you that's how you
win games in this league.
>> Brad,
>> did you see enough from Frasier to maybe
get a start there this week? And
>> uh, that's hard to say. I don't I don't
I can't say that. Now, that being said,
every rep he gets is only going to help
him. I mean, that's those are real reps
against real dudes, real opponents. Um,
and that's the most significant reps
he's had. It's not even close. I mean,
he hasn't there. Again, you do the best
you can in practice, and he's gotten
some good stuff with Mack and those
guys, but we're talking about maybe
three weeks of practice and uh maybe a
100 reps if he's lucky in practice. So,
now that being said, do I want to play
him? I'd love to play him some more.
Is Mahogany close? I mean, how close is
Mahogany?
>> We'll probably try to get him some work
this week. I don't know. A lot of it's
going to be what does he look like this
week? And and honestly, I don't expect a
lot right now, this week, you know, but
I do think he's starting to feel good
enough to to work him into [music]
practice.
>> Ways and just the critical nature of of
getting them. I don't think it was by
accident that that your linebacker got a
couple of them with Jack's punch and
Derrick's first regulation or regular
season pick. How critical are they that
linebacking core especially with the
injuries to the secondary going forward
here?
>> They're big and they're one of the
reasons I all those guys uh you know
were were a factor but those man we put
a lot on our backers the other day you
know some of those coverages we were
playing a lot of them that puts an
enormous amount of stress on your
linebackers. I thought Alex played
really well. I thought Barnes played
really well. Jack Campbell was all over
the field but to your point that was a
concerted effort man. Jack Jack almost
got three more of them out. I mean, he
got his hands on three other ones. Um,
so he's going after the football. He
looks like he does in practice. That's
what he looks like in practice. He goes
after the football and he's not just
punching blind. Doesn't mean every once
in a while he doesn't coalcock one of
our own guys, but he sees it, man. He's
going after the football. And really all
of Alex almost had one. Um, we actually
got in there and a tackle was made, but
Alex was coming up from behind. He was
about to get one out. So, the guys are
going after the football and it shows,
man. It pays dividends. You go after the
football, you see what you hit. You make
a concerted effort. One of your
teammates gets him wrapped up. The other
one comes in there and takes the ball
away. Bite the football. And uh we got
to do it again. We have to
>> Dan, obviously the Stafford traded a
long time ago, but is that a win-win
deal for both teams? I mean, you look at
what that did for you and obviously what
it did for them. Is that rare?
>> Look, I know we're excited and I'm sure
they're excited. So I, you know, however
you want to look at it, I know on our
end, we're we're fortunate to have the
guy we have and to get uh all that we
were able to get. We've got SU, we got
Saint, we got uh a lot of good players,
and we got golf. So um so I know it
feels like a win for us, and I'm sure
they do, too.
[music]
Heat.
Heat. N. [music]
[music]